

Manu Jain

board member Ahmedabad

Summary

MBA/ Engineer with 1 year experience in channel management

Seen company's exit Seen company's IPO Likely to Explore

Not a job hopper

Passout from prestigious college IIT Pass out Top 100 India Colleges

Top 100 India Engineering Colleges Top 100 India MBA Colleges

Experience

board member

WorkIndia - Jan 2020 - Present . 4 Yrs 1 Mos.

500 employees | early_stage | More Details

Human Resources | Recruiting | Staffing Agency |

managing director, indian subcontinent - india, bangladesh,

• nepal, bhutan and sri lanka

Xiaomi - Jan 2018 - Nov 2019 . 1 Yrs 10 Mos.

10000+ employees | public | More Details

Consumer Electronics Internet Mobile

vice president, xiaomi and managing director, xiaomi india

Xiaomi - Jan 2017 - Nov 2017 . 10 Mos.

10000+ employees | public | More Details

Consumer Electronics Internet Mobile

managing director, xiaomi india

Xiaomi - May 2014 - Mar 2014 . - 1 Mos.

10000+ employees | public | More Details

Consumer Electronics Internet Mobile

Responsibilities

Country Manager and head of Xiaomi's India business.

managing director

Xiaomi India - May 2014 - Nov 2016 . 2 Yrs 6 Mos.

1402 employees | Self/Funded/Govt/Others | More Details
Internet | Mobile |

board member

<u>∠estMoney</u> - Mar 2020 - Apr 2021 . 1 Yrs 1 Mos.

1000 employees | mid_stage | More Details

Big Data | Consumer Lending | Financial Services | FinTech |

board member

Hungama Digital Media Entertainment - Nov 2017 - Dec 2019 . 2 Yrs 1 Mos.

500 employees | Self/Funded/Govt/Others | More Details

Internet Music Video

board member

Krazybee - Nov 2017 - May 2019 . 1 Yrs 6 Mos.

1000 employees | Self/Funded/Govt/Others | More Details

Financial Services Lending Shopping

co-founder and managing director

<u>Jabong.com</u> - Feb 2012 - Jan 2014 . 1 Yrs 11 Mos.

536 employees | early_stage | More Details

Beauty E-Commerce Fashion Jewelry Shoes Toys

Responsibilities

* Established Jabong.com as India's leading fashion & lifestyle player - largest assortment across 10 categories, with 1000+ brands and 100,000+ unique SKUs. Integral in establishing and growing the company from inception. Apart from giving overall direction to the co., I used to head the entire demand generation - sales, marketing, TV & brand advertising, digital marketing, strategic alliances, PR, and business intelligence.

co-creator

dink couple - Aug 2011 - Dec 2012 . 1 Yrs 4 Mos.

Self/Funded/Govt/Others

Responsibilities

Co-creator of cartoon series: DINK Couple, inspired by our real life experiences.

Check out www.facebook.com/dink.couple

engagement manager

McKinsey & Company - May 2007 - Dec 2011 . 4 Yrs 7 Mos.

10000+ employees | Self/Funded/Govt/Others | More Details

Business Development | Consulting | Management Consulting |

Responsibilities

Best finishing school one can attend! I enjoyed my time at the firm, and wouldn't have done it any differently. Worked across multiple functions and sectors, such as sales & marketing, retail, FMCG, automobiles, metal & mining and more.

summer intern

tata administrative services - Apr 2006 - Jun 2006 . 2 Mos.

Self/Funded/Govt/Others

Responsibilities

Worked with Tata TeleServices for planning their national rural operations

senior associate

Headstrong - May 2003 - May 2005 . 2 Yrs 0 Mos.

Self/Funded/Govt/Others

Responsibilities

* For the 1st time, got exposed to the power of computers and internet - developed software solutions for i-banks. * Surprised myself by developing great (?) software solutions.

Education

Master OF Business Administration (M.B.A), management

2006-2006 - escp business school

bachelors, mechanical engineering

1999-2003 - Indian Institute of Technology (IITD), Delhi

bachelors, mechanical engineering

0 - Indian Institute of Technology (IITD), Delhi

Master OF Business Administration (M.B.A),

0 - Indian Institute of Management (IIM-C), Calcutta

Bachelor Of Technology (B.Tech/B.E), Mechanical

0 - Other